2018-12-04 Pro2_Fimware_V6.10

1. Fixed intput lag when more than three players problem.

----------------------------------------------------------

Firmware update instruction
1. Download the firmware file first from http://support.8bitdo.com/ 
2. Press and hold L1+R1+START buttons on the controller to put it on its update mode. LED on the top will blink in red.
3. Connect the controller to your Windows or macOS via the USB-C cable. 
4. Click on “USB Upgrade” on your device, search for bluetooth_firmware.dat in the pop-up window and run it;  
5. Un-plug the gamepad when the upgrade process is done, then restart it before using. 