2019-02-19		Firmware v1.30 for Windows & MacOS
1. Enhance the accuracy of joystick.
2. Fixed intput lag when more than three players problem.

2018-10-11		Firmware v1.29 for Windows & MacOS
1. Fixed the Name error when work on USB.

----------------------------------------------------------

Firmware update instruction
1. Download the firmware file first from http://support.8bitdo.com/ 
2. Press and hold START+L1+R1 buttons on the controller to put it on its update mode. LED on the top will blink in red.
3. Connect the controller to your Windows or macOS via the USB-C cable. 
4. Click on “USB Upgrade” on your device, search for bluetooth_firmware.dat in the pop-up window and run it;  
5. Un-plug the gamepad when the upgrade process is done, then restart it before using. 